<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Engifest2017</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sponsors">SponsorsActivity</string>
    <string name="film_Making">Parchhayi, the photography and film-making society of DTU is going to organise a
short film making competition. Selected entries will be screened at the venue with the presence of the judges.
\n\n
1  Team size: Maximum 15 members (including the actors)
\n 2.  Time Limit: Upto 15 minutes
\n 3.  Theme: To Be Announced(One month before Engifest ’17)
\n 4.  Judging Criteria:
\n Editing, Cinematography, Script, Acting, Sound design and Overall impact.
\n 5.  General Rules:
\n The movies should be either in Hindi or English or both.
\n If you choose to make a film in Hindi, it must contain English subtitles. No other languages will be allowed.
\n Please note that we will not be responsible for postal delays, losses or damages–
\n make sure you send in entries sufficiently before the deadline.
\n\nYou may use any video camera you deem suitable for shooting the movie. However, we strongly discourage low-resolution cameras, including webcams and mobile-phone cameras.
\n\n The content of the movie should be appropriate for public screening and thus should have no vulgarity.
\n\n Obscenity (at the discretion of the judges) of any kind is not allowed and will lead to immediate disqualification.
\n\n Entries must be the original work of the entrants and must not infringe third-party's rights.
\n\n Please avoid photo slideshows, remixes, spoofs and advertisements. Plagiarism is strictly prohibited.
\n Sound track can be borrowed, but with due credit.
</string>
</resources>
