<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Engifest2017</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sponsors">SponsorsActivity</string>
    <string name="Anusanthan">GROUP
\n1.   For folk, teams have to perform one of the following dance forms:
\n  Alkap, Bhangra, Bhavai, Bihu, Cheraw (bamboo dance) , Chhau, Dhap, Dumhal, Gambhira, Garba(dandiya), Gaur dance, Ghoomar, Ghumura, Giddha, Gondhal, Jawara ,Jhoomer, Kalbelia, Karakattam, Koli, Lavani, Naga dance, Odissi, Padhar, Raas.
\n If team wants to perform a form other than those mentioned above, they are required to contact the coordinators well in advance.
\n 2.   All forms of pure Indian classical dance forms are allowed.
\n 3.	Semi-classical styles are allowed provided there are distinctive classical elements are identified in the performance, amalgamated with other fusion styles. Contact the event coordinator in case of any queries.
\n 4.   The teams must bring CDs/ Pen-drive for the music (audio format)
\n 5.   Time Limit:
\n Minimum: 7 minutes
\n Maximum: 10 minutes.
\n (One minute will be allowed in addition to maximum time for setup and strike of props)
\n 6.   Team size:
\n Minimum: 6
\n Maximum: 15
\n 7.	Judging Criteria:Choreography, Synchronization, Expression, Creativity, Prop Usage, Costume, Energy, Stage coverage, and overall impact.
\n 8.  All props are allowed except for the following:
\n Swords, knives, or any other sharp objects (unless plastic – but must be approved prior to performance)
\n Fire in any form (candles, torches, etc.)
\n Fog or smoke Helium balloons Special lighting
\n
\n
\n SOLO
\n
\n
\n
\n ROUND 1: Online Prelims:
\n PARTICIPANTS ARE SUPPOSED TO SEND A VIDEO OF THEIR PERFORMANCE(MAXIMUM: 6
\n MINUTES, CLASSICAL/SEMI-CLASSICAL/FOLK) TO  nrityangana.dtu@gmail.com LATEST BY
\n
\n 12TH FEBRUARY 2017.
\n
\n
\n 1.   All forms of pure Indian classical dance forms are allowed.
\n 2.	Semi-classical styles are allowed provided there are distinctive classical elements are identified in the performance, amalgamated with other fusion styles. Contact the event coordinator in case of any queries.
\n 3.   For folk, teams have to perform one of the following dance forms:
Alkap, Bhangra, Bhavai, Bihu, Cheraw (bamboo dance) , Chhau, Dhap, Dumhal, Gambhira,Garba (dandiya), Gaur dance, Ghoomar, Ghumura, Giddha, Gondhal, Jawara
,Jhoomer, Kalbelia, Karakattam, Koli, Lavani, Naga dance, Odissi, Padhar, Raas.


If a participant wants to perform a form other than those mentioned above, they are required to contact the coordinators well in advance.
\n 4.	Time Limit(Online Prelims): Minimum: 4 minutes Maximum: 7 minutes.
(One minute will be allowed in addition to maximum time for setup and strike of props)
\n 5.   Judging Criteria:
\n
\n      Choreography, Synchronization, Expression, Creativity, Prop Usage, Costume, Energy, Stage coverage, and overall impact.
\n All props are allowed except for the following:
\n Swords, knives, or any other sharp objects (unless plastic – but must be approved prior to performance)
\n Fire in any form (candles, torches, etc. Fog or smoke
\n
\n
\n
\n Helium balloons
\n Special lighting
\n
\n
\n
\n ROUND 2: ONE ON ONE FACE OFF BATTLE
\n
\n
\n THE SELECTED CONTESTANTS WILL MOVE FORWARD TO ROUND TWO, IN WHICH THEY WILL BATTLE AGAINST A FELLOW CONTESTANT(FACE OFF) ON THE SONG CHOSEN BY THE ORGANISERS. THE PARTICIPANTS SHALL PERFORM THEIR SELECTED CLASSICAL/SEMI- CLASSICAL/FOLK DANC STYLE ON SONGS THAT MAY NOT BE OF THE SAME GENRE.
\n
\n
\n **In case of conflicts, decision of the judges would be considered final and binding**
\n
\n
\n For queries, contact:
\n
\n
\n Aditi Maheshwari
\n 9717481156
</string>
    <string name="BOB"></string>
    <string name="DoReMiPa">SponsorsActivity</string>
    <string name="film_Making">Parchhayi, the photography and film-making society of DTU is going to organise a
short film making competition. Selected entries will be screened at the venue with the presence of the judges.
\n\n
1  Team size: Maximum 15 members (including the actors)
\n 2.  Time Limit: Upto 15 minutes
\n 3.  Theme: To Be Announced(One month before Engifest ’17)
\n 4.  Judging Criteria:
\n Editing, Cinematography, Script, Acting, Sound design and Overall impact.
\n 5.  General Rules:
\n The movies should be either in Hindi or English or both.
\n If you choose to make a film in Hindi, it must contain English subtitles. No other languages will be allowed.
\n Please note that we will not be responsible for postal delays, losses or damages–
\n make sure you send in entries sufficiently before the deadline.
\n\nYou may use any video camera you deem suitable for shooting the movie. However, we strongly discourage low-resolution cameras, including webcams and mobile-phone cameras.
\n\n The content of the movie should be appropriate for public screening and thus should have no vulgarity.
\n\n Obscenity (at the discretion of the judges) of any kind is not allowed and will lead to immediate disqualification.
\n\n Entries must be the original work of the entrants and must not infringe third-party's rights.
\n\n Please avoid photo slideshows, remixes, spoofs and advertisements. Plagiarism is strictly prohibited.
\n Sound track can be borrowed, but with due credit.
</string>
</resources>
